intimateweddings.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy | Intimate Weddings - Small Wedding Blog - DIY Wedding Ideas for Small and Intimate Weddings - Real Small Weddings

You value your privacy, and so do we. That’s why we will not sell, distribute, or share any of your personally identifiable information to companies or organizations outside of IntimateWeddings.com.

As of the update of this privacy policy the membership section of this site where user data is collected is used solely for the purpose of allowing users to save favorite venues and choose to receive the IntimateWeddings.com newsletter. Thats it. Nothing else.

We also collect information from venue owners and vendors who sign up for listings on the site. The information that is collected are venue owner and vendor contact names and email addresses. Payments for advertising on the site are processed securely using the PayPal payment gateway, or optionally via check or credit card over the phone. Credit card information communicated to IntimateWeddings.com via telephone is not held by us after being processed by TD Merchant Services.

This site uses cookies for the benefit of users as well as for tracking website usage via Google Analytics. 

The site serves Google Adsense ads where cookies and/or web beacons served by Google are placed on our site in order to target ads relevant to visitors and the content on the site. Users who want to familarize themselves with Google’s privacy policy are encouraged to click through to the [google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/).

The site may serve ads from the Chitika ad network. You can read their privacy policy [here](http://chitika.com/privacy).

The site serves ads from the Brideclick.net ad network. You can read their privacy policy [here](http://brideclick.net/privacy-policy/).

The site serves ads from the Glam Publisher Network. You can read their privacy policy [here](http://www.glammedia.com/about_glam/legal/privacy.php).

We allow these and other third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

We reserve the right to make changes to our privacy policy and will post changes on our website.

– Christina Friedrichsen

_Updated Feb 25, 2013._
